It's been nearly a year since Bitcoin
hit its high of 125k.
Back in August, told you guys, all
right, here's the hard part, but I need
to put it on record so I can refer back
to it like I'm doing now and repost it
when it's time cuz that's always fun.
Slowly taking profit on ETH, BTC, and
anything else that trends up from here
at 4600 for ETH and up. Slowly building
up a stablecoin position so I can DJ in
when the bear market hits. Well, bear
market's here. Before we get into that,
it's been a while since I've been here
on YouTube. And I'm sure a lot of you
guys were like, "Yo, what's up? What's
up with more? What happened to more? Did
you abandon more?" No, man. I just
learned that you shouldn't tell
everybody what you're doing.
You should build quietly,
come up with your [music] ideas, chisel
them during the bear market, make them
the best, build them, and then present
them in the bear market when there's not
anything going on. So, this is called
Fuel. Really the type of thing that I'm
sure you guys have been waiting and
looking and searching for something to
go into. I have, but nobody will build
anything.
So, I went ahead and just built what I
would want. I came up with the perfect
game that I want to play. So, be on the
lookout for that. Follow me on Twitter.
Follow the Telegram. Links are both in
the description. And it's a wrap for
these things.
It's a wrap.
I can just keep on building on top. I
can really just do that now. I can just
keep building on top of more. It's It's
actually pretty exciting. All right,
back to the macro. I don't want to make
this video about me being right cuz
that's not what this is about. This is
about getting bullish, okay? It's time
to start getting bullish. I'm not saying
that the bottom is in or anything, but
it's time to start getting bullish
again. It's not time to be sitting
around doom scrolling and looking at AI
slop. It's time to lock in. Now is the
time to actually lock in, not back here.
I mean, lock in profits, but now is the
time to lock in, start DCA'ing the coins
that you know are going to go up, and
it's very few of them. There's Bitcoin.
There's Ethereum. There's more.
Why are you guys laughing? More is Let's
look at it. 5 cents, 20k liquidity, 100k
market cap. Come on, man. It's like a
feather, bro. It's literally a feather.
4k in pooled more, 16k in pooled ETH.
I'm not trying to make you guys FOMO or
anything, but it's time to lock in on
the core cryptos, Bitcoin, Ethereum, and
more. Now, what I'm looking for is I'm
looking at 58,000. I'm looking at this
area right in here. We're coming to a
head. I'm thinking this area right in
here. But, I think we get one more
shakeout. People got pretty bullish just
now because of Robinhood, which is
number 21, seventh in 24-hour fees,
third in DEX volume, right above
Ethereum. Now, Robinhood is really
bullish for Ethereum. I'm not going to
really mess with it because I don't need
to degen. I just need to protect what
I've gotten to this point. So, I'm just
focusing on the high caps, but this is
great for Ethereum because it burns ETH.
So, people are bridging over to
Robinhood, they're using ETH for gas,
and it's burning the ETH. So, this is
great for Ethereum. So, I'm actually
leaning more bullish on Ethereum than
Bitcoin because of that right now. And I
don't think Robinhood is going anywhere,
you know, just like Coinbase isn't. So,
um
the past couple of weeks, ETH's been
outperforming Bitcoin, and that's
because of Robinhood. Now, overall, we
zoom out, it's been getting spanked by
Bitcoin, but I think it is due to take
all of that back. Maybe it won't, maybe
it will. That's why I basically hold
Bitcoin and Ethereum equal proportions.
So, when when one is doing well, I'm
kind of not like, "Oh, I need to put it
all in Bitcoin." I just have both of
them and I'm chilling. Now, what am I
doing now? Well, the main thing is I'm
focusing on Bitcoin stock to flow. I
know I know you hear me talk about this
all the time, but this is basically the
key to financial freedom. Like it's
proven. I say this I've been saying this
for probably about 6 years now since the
last bull run. I'm going to just keep
sticking with this chart, not even
looking at this down here. This down
here is irrelevant. This right here is
"Oh, no, why is this going down here and
why is this green? This not going up."
Not even focusing on that anymore. I
never was. Focusing on only where we are
in relation to the having. When we are
anywhere between 400 to 600 days before
the having, that is peak time. Has been
the peak time to start accumulating
Bitcoin. I'm not getting into altcoins.
I have my altcoins. I still have all my
crypto, guys. I still have my
IOST if I know where the keys are. Like
I have every coin still. I don't know
what I don't even look at my portfolio.
They could be mooning right now. I
wouldn't even know.
I just keep them. I'm not looking to buy
any more cryptos. I'm looking to
continue building my Bitcoin position
for life. Continuing to build my ETH
position for life. And I'm also And I'm
accumulating SpaceX, which I should buy
some now for life. I mean, cuz I mean,
if this thing ever gets to Mars,
bro, and they start
sending rocket ships to mine it, man,
this could be a really good investment,
you know, for the long term. But if you
don't have to go in I'm not getting into
that. Focusing on this chart, Bitcoin
stock to flow. Time to buy. I've been
buying Bitcoin every day since this
thing started to look like it's even
turning green, you know, since it
started turning green I've been buying
every day. Same with Ethereum, not so
much cuz I'm earning Ethereum through
all the stuff that I've been doing. Zen,
Titan, X, I'm still getting that stuff,
selling it for ease, you know, just
that's how I'm kind of building my ETH
position. And then I'm using the funds
that I have from selling the top to buy
back Bitcoin and live. Basically trying
to survive out here. So, I'm just
accumulating Bitcoin and building
building fuel. I got two other protocols
that are semi-done. Um but I'm pretty
sure this is going to be the first one,
Fuel. It's the one I'm the most excited
about right now. The others I could keep
on tweaking and I just want to keep
launching dApps, bro, for More. Like I
could just do that. Just keep launching
dApps for More. And More is a capped
supply. Just keep pushing against that,
burning all that until there ain't no
coins left, and there's a huge thick
liquidity, and just keep on doing that.
And just make it unruggable. Just keep
on building on top of it. Pushing into
the LP pools, pushing into the buy and
burns, and just keep building, just keep
stacking the assets,
and stop fooling around with other
people. I got my own thing. Building my
own games to play.
That's what I'm doing.
Um
while buying Ethereum, accumulating,
staking ETH. That's what I'm doing. So,
stay tuned. We're back, man.
I think it's safe to say
it's time to come back, get back in the
rhythm of posting content,
and growing the community, saying what's
up to all my people. Leave a comment.
We back, man. Links to everything are
down below. If you want to check out
Fuel, the white paper is coming soon.
Follow me on Twitter.
The link is in the description. Telegram
is in the description. And I'll talk to
you guys in the next one.